<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<spob name="Kel'ar Iy">
 <pos x="3052.526056" y="6.191737"/>
 <GFX>
  <space>4-V 90.webp</space>
  <exterior>Kel'ar Iy.webp</exterior>
 </GFX>
 <presence>
  <faction>Kel'ariy</faction>
  <base>500.000000</base>
  <bonus>250.000000</bonus>
  <range>3</range>
 </presence>
 <general>
  <class>4-V</class>
  <population>1</population>
  <hide>1.000000</hide>
  <services>
   <land/>
   <refuel/>
   <bar/>
   <missions/>
   <commodity/>
   <outfits/>
   <shipyard/>
  </services>
  <description>This is a V-class planet with an enormous artificial ring which the Polaris found intact. The best theory on how it was constructed is that the materials were taken from the relatively small gas giant also in the system, which used to be much larger. The haze surrounding it, which is thought to be around 500,000 years old, and will last another 1.5 million before collapsing, is the remains of that process. This is both the capital of the Polaris and the homeworld of the Kel'ariy, the leadership caste. Interestingly, the Kel'ariy come from all the other castes and have to be chosen by the members of their own caste; the only criterion is that they be over a century old. The ruling council has four members from the Nil'kemorya, six from the Ver'ash, eight from the Tre'pira, five from the P'aedt and one from the Mu'hari. In addition, there is the leader who is given the title Bis.</description>
  <bar>This bar is filled with a number of brown-cloaked members of the leadership caste. You notice the presence of eight gray-cloaked warriors standing in pairs in a rough diamond around one of the Kel'ariy. Despite their air of relaxation, you notice that they seem to be aware of everything, and you feel their gaze bore into you whenever you make even the smallest of moves.</bar>
 </general>
 <tech>
  <item price_mod="0.500000">Foodstuffs</item>
  <item price_mod="1.330000">Luxury Goods</item>
  <item price_mod="1.500000">Data Crystals</item>
 </tech>
</spob>
